[Music]
sound me freely
asaki you made Mishi no deed is
forgotten
after
the best swordmaster in the world yes
like you I was undeserving of his
patience I agree mission complete
next time you should leave it to me
I can spy upon our enemies
unseen and undetected
pain and Agony and what am I man
or machine I wanted to be able to walk
again
the extraction point is in here push
them back they are breaking through
they are going to break through
the door is almost destroyed
he did not find them to his liking Talon
once tried to recruit my father their
aims did not coincide with his own
they seem determined to kill us life on
death balance on the edge of my blade
Merry Christmas
a nice attempt but I must return our
flag now returning the flag to base
Smiles upon me he cannot take much more
attack Focus all our attacks upon the
objective it will soon be destroyed
[Music]
focus our attacks upon the objective
destroy the objective
Eradicator destroyed
I am defending enemy passion eliminated
we must stop the payload progress
drive them off the payload
we need to stand in the payloads way get
to cover
get ready that door is coming down
that fitting in for the Assassin
assassin assassin eliminated
our enemies possess a teleporter enemy
teleporter detected they are above us
watch above you they are attacking from
behind
on your left
they are meeting us head-on below us
they are coming from below watch the
left side
here they come on the right enemy on the
right
No Way Out not this way it's as though
the whole city has been mobilized
against us
still knows how to rescue the battle
continues
objective complete my ultimate is
charged attack with me take him down
yeah yeah
you're welcome
find a teleporter she's on you assassins
on you I need armor I require armor
simple reporting in I'm over here
patience is not my strong suit bridging
device set now we wait
count your blessings defend the
objective touche
my skills improve
ways home for either of us then I
believe you heard wrong
we are all of us always changing so that
others may look upon me without fear or
pity what is stronger the hammer or the
sword does it bother you that I can
summon a dragon why do you ask
do you have an idea about how to break
your curse watch yourself master I
cannot mind your back at all times
it is one of the legendary plays of my
family
I manage your help to repair my sword
and armor when the battle is done it is
strange to see you taking part in a
Battle Master why do you hunt dragons
battle is not your way
I am only just getting started
hmm
[Laughter]
we must defend our flag
defend our flag
we need a Healer I require healing I
need healing did you hear that
I'm guessing this isn't because of the
storm
prepare yourselves
let's get that truck moving this dinner
is cited eyes here watch here be careful
coal and snow Guided by the wind
no hint of a breeze
I turn your momentum against you
not everyone escapes their fate you will
not find the answer you seek I am
victorious this time brother
the wind blows in my favor
no need to check on me doctor do you
know
your actions continue to haunt you my
aim is true
a strong wind can fill any tree
your focus lacks Focus master
thank you zionova
Precision is the way of the effective
Warrior
forever hold your peace
I cherish every victory
your choices lead to your fate quite the
battle
foreign
a simple Victory watch your next move
that was almost a challenge this is the
end for you
no need to go easy on me master early
blossoms fall from the tree either
you can my deadliest enemy
defeated
until next time
it's coming straight at us it's coming
over the bridge
the door has been damaged the door is
under attack
protectador it seems we sprang the Trap
I am the sword in the shadows they must
not outpace us how did they catch up we
are about to lose the lead you are only
human
slicer destroyed
My ultimate is almost ready enemy scene
enemy here I see one we need to get on
board
our enemies have the upper hand for now
let us turn the tables
there's no time to dwell in the past now
we fight
what's the right side it's coming from
the right
it's too early for Dusty bloom
cheers tressor
[Music]
back at you brother
retaliation is Swift
calm down Winston bombs away
think fast pharah back to you
the storm moves quickly this is not a
snowball fight
just like in training an unseen enemy is
near
enemy detected I sense the presence of
the enemy
take down the objective we need to take
out the target my blade never dulls
someone rigged a truck to blow get ready
strikes the sword is an elegant weapon
for more civilized age
stop the robot follow the path this way
claiming the objective join me on the
objective the objective is in my hands
now we push do not falter the barricade
must stay in motion let us move the
barricade over there
my allies will return soon
I am strong but with a team I am
stronger a moment alone before my allies
return
over here she's the only one who's awake
late at night on base he also is so
beautiful it reminds me of home
he does seem a bit dramatic doesn't he
and I'm the only one who can drink her
coffee the storm is getting worse I
understand
understood very well
do not let the deteronator get near push
the robot that robot must move item
dropped damn dropped it it's coming over
the wrong Parts on the left the lead is
ours pushing ahead the lead has been
taken push ahead Take the Lead let us
move with certainty our flag is in the
open get it back they have dropped our
flag
strike quickly and hold their movement
the enemy is pushing their barricade the
enemy moves we must stop them your
reflexes are slow
that was both of you after you
I learned that from my brother
how foolish your hand-to-hand needs to
work only a fool wastes an opportunity
you are as dangerous as your storm when
the path is clear one walks with
confidence even zifter thanks to you I'm
very hurt I've been hit
shutting down
Talon's money is lining his pockets
he's our first talent lead since Venice
it will be my pleasure
thanks for helping me out earlier Angela
qualities quality maybe he just likes to
look at it he doesn't strike me as a
drinker I had nothing to do with it
he'll talk I was a bystander translation
he's soft I'll watch here I will watch
this position
watching here Harry we must take the
robot
final push capture the robot no we need
to stop her press the attack we need to
revive our teammate our teammate is down
I'll cut a path through these Talent
soldiers
I'm watching her for you Angela the
enemy surrounds us the enemy outnumbers
us
trick or treat you fought well those men
just not well enough Amari chose poorly
you have the advantage but I had the
edge
your soul work needs work head to the
Waypoint report to the objective
we must reach the objective proceed to
the objective our course is clear let's
go pick up complete I have it secured I
believe I have pictures if that is the
case our enemies have much to fear let
us proceed with haste you have an
admirable piece about you
this should be a place of reflection and
learning
it saddens me that it is in danger
I could ask the same of you oh I'm sorry
hinda we are the same
Talon you are lucky I did not Cut You
Down where you stand I do not say
we will be the lightning the rise the
storm I still feel that final Blow from
yesterday's training I make my own
among other things
it only happened once
I remember this place
there is always a way to make something
from nothing brother
a battle's end calls for meditation not
games but
you don't breathe and when you meet the
less than innocent mental bearing not
skill is a sign of a mature Warrior yeah
Triceratops my cybernetic form came a
great cost
but you ask to change master how do you
maintain your Tranquility amid endless
battles no I have not
hero was not easy
living in your shadow
fine I'll go
my vision was cluttered by anger at
times I can almost hear the voices of
those who lost their lives here
I live brother
why are you still grieving my sword and
your Hammer will lead us to Victory we
should begin and left me a monster like
other creations you care too much about
how the family perceived you I still
have much to learn
yes you didn't want to be the only one
he won't tell me either we should
continue to the extraction point was
that a joke you're a surgeon of course
no I find it strangely reassuring
perhaps because you saved my life they
did not feel a part of me I am grateful
for our conversations Angela I hope we
may resume them when we return to base
I wouldn't know they have pushed ahead
of us we fall behind the enemy has the
lead
through here this way for a moment you
are weightless
farewell
we are at The Distillery break through
the door we must break through let's
make our own path final push keep the
robot close
this is our last chance to take the
robot we must defend the robot Last
Chance protect the robot
why do you ask protector what we cannot
let them take the robot do not leave the
robot that class gather on the horizon a
storm is coming I'll be watching your
back Angela
not that you really need me Max is
getting away we should hurry I sense a
trap the dragon and I oh one we have the
robot robot secured come a robot
everyone needs to group up join me
I found the objective you are welcome to
join me come to my position
all bark no bite someone is hunting us
one of the Assassins is here fall back
slicers dispatch them quickly clear the
area
enemy Shield generator destroyed
their Shield generator is no more time
is against us press on the end of this
battle is near
my enemies topple session
The Winds of death are strong
it comes to this do not falter after
this there will be only one Victor
Talon Trooper head
no yeah
hmm
tour
sure
out kill the Assassin we need to move
together
group up here
find me here group here quick join me
gather to me group up join me a worthy
Foe for my blade the enemy is here
I see the enemy okay
so
time is running out strike them now
there's no time to lose attack
clear the payloads path the payload
progresses the payload is moving
someone begin bridge in the door hello
foreign what are we waiting for
what is the delay
someone want to handle that capture the
enemy flag
we must attack the enemy flag sit up
here
oh
the Assassin is back in the shadows
she disappeared where did she go
in three two one
three two one
each
side then
I need a dancing
let's say Zen
are you singing
watch for the sniper sniper head smoke
watch for Sniper I have found the shield
generator
no matter what I do I cannot Escape my
fate who was Antonio
I believe you found an experienced
solution Commander my Halloween costume
cyborg ninja the enemy terrapora is no
longer concern
Josh enemy teleporter destroyed
we need more time to bridge the door now
Troopers bought it it was nothing
it is an honor Nana
is
my duty calls I continue on this path
mistakes will always precede Victory
each Journey has its trials finally a
real challenge
or 14 deploying get ready to engage
admirable a worthy strike
teach me that one master
masterful a fine shot brother hey that's
my technique expert work
you make everything look easy
a worthy strike side by side again
cowboy
we lost one moira's down taking
casualties our enemies have deployed a
shield generator
incoming my work here is done
get out of there move
to know yourself is to be at peace push
that payload move the payload giving up
the flag
dropping the flag eliminate the target
behind you yo
hello
hello hi greetings ah yes
[Laughter]
stop the payload Victory approaches we
must see through
the fight is almost over keep defending
time works against them don't lose focus
my power is trained my body is
compromised ah
I will make use of this what treasure is
this
something for my trouble a worthy reward
Just My Style
I moved to strike
I am healed arigato
I am restored
the objective is damaged yush an
assassin
I know you're kind there she is
just like old times
foreign I feel no remorse for the fate
of these criminals
it makes no difference to me
stealth has long since been an
impossibility
Isis
a dragon the witch is here the monster
is Among Us the reaper emerges from the
Shadows Dr jangenstein is here
sniper be Rarity push forward
sorry
about that I'm pinned help assassin's on
me get off me I'll talk to the objective
yes enemy turret destroyed I require
assistance I need help and force ain't
coming
our enemy craves another defeat her work
is efficient as always the enemy returns
the enemy has been revived take the
objective let us coordinate our attacks
upon the objective are all the Warriors
of your land women let us hope that this
time it works out better in the end
I have learned much from him a little
about him
you move as well as any swordsman I know
take out the enforcer
foreign
[Laughter]
never an Eradicator
be on your guard
keep the area clear until we can depart
Genji is with you
I'm with you the witches felt the Mages
flame is extinguished the reaper is gone
for now Dr Jenkins Stein is no more John
gangstein's monster Falls
two
yep
yep Raw
someone slay the witch the monster must
be felt kill the Reaper
the Mage must be destroyed we must kill
Dr jagestein to the objective on my way
this is no time to doubt yourself
stay sharp brother be careful
we need Evac right now
you okay get back in the fight come on
it's not your day to die
I wouldn't recommend it heavy assault
unit is a weekend
he's weakened I burn like the dawn
I'm on fire
my spirit blazes
I leave flames in my wake I burn with
purpose my soul is a light power causes
through me
now
you've already lost
I am Unstoppable
our enemy has been swept away the forest
has been cut down
huh
[Music]
it should not be much longer do not
falter now I am ready
I was hoping for a challenge an enemy
Bastion be ready I will never look at
skinny the same way
we have a welcome company on the
objective the objective is under attack
cut them down they are attacking the
objective let us show them a real fight
the door is being destroyed
get them off the door they are Bridging
the door that is not what they're for
do not blame yourself for Monday that's
death
it was not your fault
s
cross for now
as to the Future
we shall see
does the suffering of the omnics hear
trouble you master why don't we find out
I am at peace with who I was your threat
does not concern me Angela I have some
chocolates for you
not Swiss
I am certain of it thank you Angela
perhaps you could share them with me my
father shojiro called me that as an
insult I've grown to like it Lim yo
though
I know what it is to leave behind a pass
you are not proud of
Johan show me what you've been working
on
I was a Reckless Youth but you are
something else entirely
that's right
wait used to
hey where did they all go
I'll pass many an hour of my Miss pants
youth here
the heart of a man still beats inside me
what is it like to have the chance to
change the past
I must
I am at peace with it I suspect you will
be forever unsatisfied
so this is what has become of you
a pity
it is beautiful here
I could never appreciate it before
Angela what did you wish for on your
tanzaku so that was your dream not mine
it was that long and a difficult Road
but now I feel at ease in my own body
just this one time
I always liked working with you Winston
no awkward small talk
I am a different man now
I am whole
he is still not ready for time to flow
forward again any chocolates today
brother
no you finally live in the challenge
nor can I
cash money
how can I convince you that I am still a
man only here do I not feel Outcast that
was another life
we shall see brother
empty your mind focus on the task at
hand
this is my home now
all my best behavior Captain this
reminds me of our time on base in
Switzerland
doomfist you are truly a worthy foe I
will strike our enemies where they do
not expect what would our father think
of what we've become brother
it is not too late to change your course
brother
and you master
orisa you grow stronger each time I see
you
make yourself
just setting foot here sets My Soul at
ease
I find the company more agreeable these
days
My ultimate is charging hey let me
turret ahead Detonator destroyed the
flag on Ayah one
I have the flag try and stop me taking
the flag to base
Stand Together die together
the enemy gathers here
I have claimed the flag I score for our
team
you need healing tie them up we must
reclaim our flag they have our flag
after them our enemies are weak this is
our chance we must press our advantage
and see his victory
measure twice cut once a steady blade
balances the soul
the advantage is mine
foreign my spirit grows strong
Tracer listen
able Angela
master
I will avenge you brother
oh no the Fallen
the battle commences
let's finish this quickly
like slicing through paper faster than
lightening I put the sea
slower than a tortoise don't blink next
time
foreign
let's go why has the payload stopped we
must move
get the payload movie again
I'm on it here we go
I am repaired ah much better I am healed
Go My ultimate is ready my blade is
ready to be Unleashed I'm not impressed
Show Me What You're Made Of no holding
back come at me
do your worst anyway
yeah
see
hmm
stay out of her sights now Trooper down
time to go get on board dropships here
let's go
defend the objective concentrate our
defenses are the objective going in and
force it down Victory beckons do not
falter now Victory draws near
I found a teleporter
you seem nice I hate to kill you
take cover
your eyes deceive you oh
oh
you should have stuck with a sword
okay
back at you
Rising Hammer intercepting sword
is that the best you can do
I will got the objective moving the
objective to its destination I require
Shields I need a shield
bolster our defenses protect our flag
from further incursions we must not let
that happen again
now we have our way out let's go most
enjoyable
Yosh
the dragon behind me
what happens when you run out of bullets
I am centered when this is done we
should fight together again
she's no true Dragon but surely the
Summoner is one of your enemies
track down
foreign
fear the focused Warrior
come on
very well this one's mine
they have our flag after them we must
reclaim our flag damn
so
while one lives there is hope I don't
mind these odds thanks
thank you I thank you
thanks Jenna
farewell maybe the horse has passed
the white tiger becomes me
unbreakable body
hence him
two
Genji is here
fantastic technique
break the limit
come on
the demon becomes me
okay
[Applause]
yeah
yes